Branden Ng

Front-End Web Developer Melbourne, VIC

linkedin.com/in/brandendaniel in github.com/BrandenDaniel 😱

Web Portfolio - branden.vercel.app

J 04 32 375 587

Experienced front-end web developer with a fiery passion for transforming static wireframes into interactive, beautiful spaced websites. Throughout my journey, I've had the privilege to collaborate with a diverse range of clients and businesses. I am currently learning React.js and API integrations.

Work Experience

LeasePLUS Group - SafeCode

Sept. 2022 - Present

Front-end Web Developer

Melbourne CBD, VIC

SafeCode, a LeasePLUS subsidiary, creates novated leasing and salary packaging interfaces for individuals and businesses. With 100,000+ users, they cater to diverse clients across Australia.

- Worked on proprietary leasing/salary packaging software for LeasePlus Group
- Management of all LeasePlus group's websites/portals (over 5+)

LeasePLUS Group - SalaryPackagingPLUS

Accounts Officer - salary deductions receivable & payable

Arcadian Digital &

Apr. 2022 - Sept. 2022

Melbourne CBD, VIC

Sept. 2019 - Feb. 2020 Melbourne CBD. VIC

Junior Front-end Web Developer

As a bespoke digital and marketing agency, Arcadian deliver tailored solutions to organisations of all sizes. I worked with extremely talented engineers during my time there.

- Collaborative work with project managers and lead/senior developers
- · Build and structure WordPress child themes
- Build and maintan the company's own WordPress plugins and themes

Bebble Media &

May. 2018 - Jun. 2019

North Laverton, VIC

Junior Front-end Web Developer

A small digital agency in West Melbourne with in-house designers and developers. Specialising in WordPress, they assist small business owners in expanding their ecommerce and online presence.

- Collaborate with web/graphic designers to reach mockup standards
- Integrations of plugins + customisation of plugins to suit client's specifics
- Manipulation of software styles (i.e plugins, themes) exact to design mockups

Tech Stack & Skills Interests & Hobbies JavaScript React [HTML] css ETFs & Index Funds Personal Finance Tech | jQuery | Bootstrap | Git API integration Critically Acclaimed Films | Youtube Work **Personal Projects** MySalPack (employee portal) & 2023 My Web Portfolio & 2023 [JavaScript] [jQuery] [Sass] [Blazor] Bootstrap React | JavaScript | HTML | Sass MySalPack (employer portal) & 2022 YouTube Clone & 2023 JavaScript | | ¡Query | | Sass | | Blazor React | Material UI Rapid API Bootstrap Axios Sass Print Strategy Management & 2019 Cryptoverse & 2023 JavaScript | jQuery | WordPress | Bootstrap | CSS React | Redux | Rapid API Axios Sass Ant Design

Education

Udacity

Front End Web Developer Nanodegree

Online

Oct. 2017 - May 2018

Online

Front End Web Development Track

May - Aug. 2017

RMIT University

Team Treehouse

Melbourne, VIC Jul. 2016 - Apr. 2017

Completed 48 credits towards a Bachelor of Information Technology Relevant Courses Included:

- Web Programming
- User-centered Design